# Yubo Cao

STUDENT & PROGRAMMER

# Contact

- cao2006721@gmail.com
- (470) 854-9826
- Lawrenceville, Georgia 30044

# CAREER OBJECTIVE

I propose to primarily concentrate on contributing to the technical aspect and seminar development of the event. However, I am also conversant in the realm of organization and proficient in the realm of 2D design, and therefore stand ready to utilize these capabilities in service of HackGwinnett's success. I am confident in my expertise and experience, and fervently desire to apply these attributes towards the realization of the hackathon's full potential.

# EXPERIENCE

September 2022-now

#### Officer

Computer Science Club, Lilburn, Georgia

- Create instructional materials, plan activities, and be present at regular meetings.
- Participate in initiatives including internet, machine learning, and cybersecurity.
  Assisting members of the computer science club.

May 2022-now

## Tutor/Volunteeer

Learn To Be, Lilburn, Georgia

- Tutor students about knowledge of CS, math, and physics/chemistry
- Help students with homework and prepare for tests.

# **EDUCATION**

September 2021-now

HIGH SCHOOL GPA 4.0/4.0

Gwinnett School of Mathematics, Science, and Technology, Lilburn, Georgia

#### Relevant Coursework

- AP Biology (in progress)
- Robotics (in progress)
- AP Computer Science Principles (5/5)
- AP Calculus BC (in progress)

### Awards & Honors

- Academic achievement in mathematics (1 out of all freshmen)
- Governor's honors program nomination in mathematics, computer programming, and mechanical engineering
- Academic letter (Numeric grade average  $\geq 95$ )
- CyberPatriot state finalist

### EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- FIRST tech challenge (FTC) robotics team
- CyberPatriot (cybersecurity competition)
- Symphonic band

### SKILLS

- Microsoft Excel, Word, and PowerPoint & LATEX
- SQL (MySQL dialect)
- Python (spider, automation, data processing & visualization)
- Java & C
- Data processing, visualization, and modeling (Pandas, Matplotlib, and Sklearn)
- Linux (Debian & RHEL), Bash